本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
快点  快点  这么多总该有点动静了吧
Come on, come on. Should be just enough to finish the job.
呼  这玩意儿可得小心处置
Phew! Can't be too careful with this stuff.
事件已完成初始化
“警告” 叽里呱啦叽里呱啦
"Warning." Blah blah blah...
“过度操作会导致轻微引力反常”
"Extreme usage could result in minor gravity anomalies."
拜托  书呆子  老子都走到这一步了
Can it, Poindexter. I've come this far.
几句话可吓不倒我
I'm not giving up now.
好  就是这样
Yes, this is it!
尽管会有些震颤  不过总归是值得的
<i>It's gonna be a bumpy ride, but it'll all be worth it.</i>
再过十八个小时
Just eighteen more hours.
终于  一切将在今天被改写
<i>Finally, everything changes... today.</i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： 战忽局副局座  乔乔央央  溪傲季
时间轴  校订： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第十一集
Gravity Falls  S02E11  Not What He Seems
这里  这里  就在这里
It's here! It's here! It's here!
■
后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
来看  我本来是在随便开门玩的
Okay, so I was just opening random doors,
因为我发神经  结果我找到了好东西
because I'm a creep, when I found something amazing!
我早上七点就被拽起来  那肯定是好东西
If it was worth waking up at 7:00 am for, that will be amazing.
-大饱眼福吧  -哇
- Feast your eyes! - Whoa!
老弟  你知道我在想什么吧
Bro. Bro. We're both thinkin' it.
疯狂屋顶烟花派对
<i>Crazy rooftop fireworks party!</i>
别着急  孩子们  你们竟敢
Not so fast, kids. There is no way on Earth
非法燃放危险的烟花爆竹  我只想说
you're setting off those dangerous, illegal fireworks...
请带上我
without me.
给你点上  宝贝儿
Here you go, sweetie!
给你斯坦叔公好好放放火吧
Set something on fire for your Grunkle Stan!
我就是毁灭之神
I am the god of destruction!
你们先等下  有烟花燃放许可证吗
Hold on a minute. Do you have a permit for those?
呃  那你有傻蛋出门许可证吗
Uh, do you have a permit for being totally lame?
傻了吧
Hey-o!
你这可说到点子上了  接着玩吧
Well, I can't argue with that. Carry on.
不开玩笑  我们还是要把这烂摊子打扫干净
But seriously, though, we should probably clean this mess up.
-用水球灭火  -我觉得挺合适的
- With water balloons? - I don't see why not.
怎么搞的
Seriously?
啊  周六就该干这种傻事儿干一整天
Ah, this is what Saturdays are for. Doing dumb things forever!
傻事儿要干一整天
<i>Dumb things forever!</i>
哟  悠着点
Whoa, there!
致斯坦叔公  不光是个叔公
To Grunkle Stan! Not just a great uncle...
还是最好的叔公
The greatest uncle!
好啦好啦  跟你们讲
All right, all right. I tell ya,
姐弟俩像你们这么融洽的  还真不多见
it's unnatural for siblings to get along as well as you do.
别操心  暑假剩下的时间还多呢
Don't worry, we've still got plenty of summer left
够我们互掐了
to drive each other crazy.
呵呵  唉  暑假剩下的时间还多呢
Heh... yeah... plenty of summer left.
孩子们  有点事儿  有点事儿我该告诉你们
Kids, there's something I, uh... something I should tell you.
这事儿  呃  挺复杂的
It's, um... W-well, it's complicated.
我
I...
我再去拿点汽水喝
I'm gonna go refresh my soda.
趁着现在好好享受吧  斯坦  他们迟早会发现的
Enjoy it while you can, Stan. They'll find out sooner or later.
今天纸包不住火了  这是啥  瓢虫么
Today's the day. What is that, a ladybug?
这是怎么  哎呀完了
What the... Oh, no!
目标已被控制  准备占领房屋
Target's secure! Take the house!
这是怎么
What the... ?
小孩已被控制  索降组行动
Kids are secure. Roof team, go!
安全
Clear!
小猪已被控制  我们控制了一只小猪
Pig secure... we have secured a pig.
喂  放开我  你这跑龙套的
Hey, hands off, you stooge!
我不明白怎么回事
I don't understand!
我干了什么事迹要劳烦你们这样抓我
What did I do that warrants this much arresting?
政府探员  我还以为你们被僵尸吃了
The government guys? I thought you got eaten by zombies.
-我们活下来了  九死一生  -我用特雷格当人肉盾牌
- We survived... barely. - I used Trigger as a human shield.
-他当时哭得跟个小屁孩似的  -什么  喂
- He cried like a baby. - Wha... Hey!
怎么能当着特种兵的面讲糗事
Not in front of the special ops guys.
这是一段政府废料处理部的监控录像
This is security footage of a government waste facility.
昨晚凌晨四点钟  有人闯入偷走了约三百加仑的高危废料
<i>At 0400 hours last night, someone robbed 300 gallons of dangerous waste.</i>
什么  你觉得是我干的
What? You think that's me?
派恩斯  别想装傻糊弄我
Don't play dumb with us, Pines!
我真的什么都不知道  昨晚我在给纪念品店
But I actually am dumb! Last night I was restocking
-上货来着  我发誓  -斯坦叔公  等等
- the gift shop... I swear! - Wait, Grunkle Stan!
你们抓错人了  斯坦叔公可能偶尔可能会
You've got the wrong guy! Our Grunkle Stan might shoplift
顺走人家的橘子  但他绝不是什么超级大坏蛋
the occasional tangerine, but he's not some evil supervillain.
小朋友  听好了  我们整个夏天都在监控你们家
Listen, kid. We've been watching your family all summer,
也确实看到了点破事
and we've seen some disturbing things,
但是肯定都没有你们叔叔的小秘密危险
but nothing as dangerous as what your uncle is hiding.
小屋里藏有一台末日仪器
Somewhere hidden in this shack is a doomsday device!
特雷格  你照顾孩子们
Trigger, you take the children.
我跟老头谈谈  这么唐突真是不好意思
I'll talk to the old man. Sorry to break it to you, kids,
不过你们根本不了解你们的叔公
but you don't know your uncle at all.
-冰棍  安全  -嘿
- Icee pop, clear! - Hey!
孩子们  你们要相信我啊
Kids! You gotta believe me!
这次我真的是无辜的  孩子们啊
<i>For once I'm actually innocent! Kids!</i>
上班去啦
Headin' into work, doot doo doo doo doo
地面小组  上  上  上
Ground team, move move move!
-强行破门  -还是算了吧
- Break down the door! - Or... maybe not.
斯坦福・派恩斯  你被指控犯有  盗窃政府废料
Stanford Pines, you stand accused of theft of government waste,
酝酿阴谋  以及藏匿非法武器的罪名
conspiracy, and possession of illegal weapons.
你打算怎么给自己辩护
How do you plead to these charges?
呃  “冤罪”  啊不  “无案”
Uh... "guiltoccent." I mean, "innoguilty."
呃  我能打个电话吗
Um... Can I have my phone call?
嗯  哪款套餐送小玩具我就点哪款
Okay, give me whatever you got that comes with a free toy.
苏斯
<i>Soos!</i>
派恩斯先生  你是附身在这上面了吗
Mr. Pines? Is this some sort of possession situation?
苏斯  接电话
<i>Soos, pick up!</i>
派恩斯先生  怎么回事  听说你被抓走了
Mr. Pines, what happened? I heard you got arrested or something?
我要吃点东西压压惊
I had to go get some panic food.
听好了  你得帮我个忙
<i>Listen, I need something from you.</i>
纪念品店里的那台售货机知道吧
You know that vending machine in the gift shop?
就算命丢了也得给我守着
<i>I need you to guard it with your life.</i>
不管发生什么  不管谁跟你说什么
<i>No matter what happens, no matter who talks to you,</i>
绝对不能让任何人动售货机
<i>don't let them touch that machine!</i>
看来本修理工  要升级成修理专员了
Time for a repair guy... to become a repair man.
先生  这是您点的亲亲宝贝美味儿童套餐
<i>Sir, your Junior Yum-Yum Baby-Time Kiddo Meal?</i>
把薯条塞我嘴里
Just put one in my mouth.
我们出发吧
Let's do this.
派恩斯先生已经被拘留
<i>We've got Mr. Pines in custody.</i>
我们的队员正在小屋里搜寻那台仪器
<i>Our men are searching the shack for that device.</i>
你把小孩子照顾好
<i>You take care of those kids.</i>
你要把我们怎么样
What are you gonna do to us?
-我们会送你们去托儿所  -差劲
- We'll be taking you to child services. - Boo!
这段时间  看点儿脑残的电视真人秀吧
In the meantime, enjoy some mindless reality TV...
专门用来安抚小孩子的  还能让他们闭上嘴
designed to pacify you and make you stop asking questions.
我要开始做手术了
<i>I'm about to make the incision.</i>
整人恶作剧
<i>Ker-prank!</i>
你正在收看由贾斯汀・爱整人带来的《整人恶作剧》节目
<i>You're watching Ker-Prank'd with Justin Ker-Prank.</i>
迪普  这简直太疯狂了
Dipper, this is crazy.
斯坦叔公绝对不可能去偷高危废料的
There's no way Stan was stealing hazardous waste.
我们得为他洗清罪名
We gotta clear his name!
等等  监控录像带
Wait a minute, the security tapes!
斯坦叔公是不是说他昨晚在礼品店上货
Didn't Stan say he was restocking the gift shop last night?
如果我们能拿到神秘小屋的监控录像带
If we could get the Mystery Shack's surveillance tapes,
我们就能证明他的清白了
we could prove he's innocent!
我们只需要想个办法离开这里
We just need to think of a way out of here.
想想  梅宝  好好想想
Think, Mabel. Think.
多次乐队最棒
多次乐队被过誉了
不
No!
求救  求救  有特工受伤了
<i>Mayday, mayday! Agent down!</i>
-该死的树枝  -太好了
- Darn branch! - Yes!
请求支援  请求支援
Backup! Requesting backup!
快点  迪普  我们还要为叔公洗清罪名呢
Come on, Dipper. We're gonna go clear our uncle's name.
可怜的孩子们  你们真以为你们的叔公是清白的吗
Oh, you poor kids. You really think your uncle's innocent?
我以前见过太多这种事  用假的名字  双重身份
<i>I've seen it all before. False names, double lives.</i>
前一分钟  他们还在玩水球
<i>One minute, they're playing with water balloons.</i>
下一秒钟  他们就建起了末日装置
<i>The next, they're building doomsday devices.</i>
你们的叔公欺骗了所有人
<i>Your uncle scammed the whole world.</i>
你们还想让他继续欺骗你们吗
<i>You gonna let him scam you, too?</i>
你  你根本就不知道自己在说什么
You... You don't know what you're talking about.
你们会后悔的
<i>You're gonna regret this!</i>
只有五个小时了  我得回去
Only five more hours till it happens. I gotta be there!
斯坦  你得想个办法离开这里
Come on, Stan, you gotta think of a way out of this.
好好想想
Think! Think!
异常现象正在发生
反应越来越强烈了  对了  有办法了
They're getting stronger! Of course, that's it!
是我的错觉吗  还是地球刚刚颤抖了一下
Is it just me, or did the entire world just hiccup?
我觉得只是个小不点的地震
I'm sure it's just a baby-sized earthquake.
哦  小不点耶
Aww, baby-sized!
距启动还有
要来了  末日就要来了
It's happening! The end times!
我必须赶在机器启动之前离开小镇
When that machine activates, I gotta get outta town!
进去  我的浣熊老婆  进去
Git in there, raccoon wife, git!
好了  计划是这样的  我来搞定那两个守卫
<i>All right, here's the plan. I'll take out those</i>
你一记空手道正中另一个家伙的脖子
<i>two guard guys, you karate-chop the other dude in the neck,</i>
然后我们一串后空翻通过正门
and then we'll back-flip through the front door!
梅宝  你不觉得还有更简单的方法吗
Mabel, aren't you forgetting the simpler solution?
哦  也是
Oh, right.
-这是个石头还是张脸  -我觉得  这是个隐喻
- So is it a rock, or is it a face? - I think... it's a metaphor.
好了  如果我是斯坦叔公
All right. If I was Stan,
我会把监控录像带放在哪呢
where would I hide those surveillance tapes?
等等  羚羊兔
Wait! The Antelabbit!
你是说鹿角兔吗
Don't you mean "jackalope"?
切  你瞎说
Pfft! That can't be right.
有了
<i>Yes!</i>
这是这周的  就是它了
<i> It's this week! This is it!</i>
快  快  快  快  快
<i>Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!</i>
有人说要“虫虫舞”  所以我们就跳了
Someone yelled "Wormy Dance." We had to!
快进吧
Fast-forward.
看  就是这样  斯坦叔公在上货  就像他说的那样
<i>Ha! There it is! Stan restocking, like he said.</i>
日期显示就是昨晚  这就是证据  他是清白的
And the date shows it was last night! It's proof! He's innocent!
-啊哦  -呃  也许
- Uh-oh. - Uh, maybe he's just
也许他只是出门上厕所了  这也是正常情况
going to the bathroom outdoors, the way nature intended.
哦  不是吧  斯坦
<i>Oh, no. Stan, you didn't!</i>
别慌  我们还不知道穿着防护服的那个人是谁呢
Don't panic. That could be anyone in that suit.
热比利时华夫饼干啊
<i>Hot Belgian waffles!</i>
等等  周围没人  那还不说心里话  狗娘养
<i>Wait, I'm alone. I can swear for real! Son-of-a... </i>
这肯定是他了
That's him, all right.
好吧好吧  所以斯坦叔公也许真的偷了有毒废料
Okay, okay. So maybe Grunkle Stan stole some toxic waste.
但这不意味着他过着罪恶的双重人生
That doesn't mean he's leading a nefarious double life.
梅宝  这个我可不敢确定
Mabel, I'm not so sure about that.
什么  这都是些什么
What? What is all this?
斯坦森・潘菲尔德
Stetson Pinefield?
哈尔・福雷斯特  安德鲁・“8号球”・阿尔卡特拉斯
Hal Forrester? Andrew "8-Ball" Alcatraz?
这些都是假身份证  梅宝  普通人怎么会有这些
These are fake IDs, Mabel! You wouldn't need these
除非他想掩盖自己的真实身份
unless you were trying to hide your real identity.
但是斯坦叔公为什么要这么做
But why would Stan do that?
斯坦・派恩斯已死
什么
What?
《斯坦・派恩斯已死》
<i>"Stan Pines Dead"?</i>
“派恩斯的死疑有隐情”
<i>"Foul play suspected in Pines' death."</i>
“严重车祸  刹车失灵” 谁干的
"Fiery car crash, brakes cut... " By who?
“姓名未知的诈骗犯在逃”
<i>"Unnamed grifter at large"?</i>
为什么说他“姓名未知”
Why would they call him "unnamed"?
-除非斯坦  -不是
- Unless Stan... - ... isn't...
斯坦
<i>Stan?!</i>
斯坦・派恩斯已死
<i>Stan Pines is dead? </i>
那我们和谁住在一起呢  这根本不可能
Then who have we been living with? It doesn't make any sense!
肯定有什么合理的解释
There has to be some explanation.
也许我们上《整人恶作剧》了  贾斯汀・爱整人
Maybe we're getting Ker-Pranked! Justin Ker-Prank is gonna
就藏在某盆植物后面  随时都可能跳出来
jump up from behind one of these plants, any minute now!
跳出来吧  贾斯汀
Any minute, Justin.
难以相信  整个夏天我都在找寻重力泉谜团的答案
Can't believe it! This whole summer I've been looking for answers,
但是最大的谜团就在我们眼皮底下
and the biggest mystery was right under our nose.
这里应该能找到什么解释的  应该有的
There's gotta be some kind of explanation in here, somewhere.
这是什么 “藏身所的密码”
What the... ? "Secret Code to Hideout"?
让我看看  A1  B  C3
Let me see that! A1, B, C3...
密码
-我从来没见过这样的密码  -等等  我见过
- I've never seen a code like this. - Wait, I have!
迪普  是自动售货机
Dipper, it's the vending machine!
好了  派恩斯  游戏时间结束了
All right, Pines. Play time is over.
去华盛顿的直升机已经准备好了
Chopper's ready to dust off to Washington.
我倒是很乐意把你交出去
I'll enjoy putting you away.
什么  我们可以再等会儿吗  一分钟就好
What? Um, can't we stick around for maybe one minute,
呃  一分三十秒
uh, one minute, thirty seconds?
我们才不会中你的计呢  派恩斯
We're not falling for your games, Pines.
你已经逃亡了半辈子了  已经结束了
You've been running your whole life. Your time is finally up.
我能去趟厕所吗  只要十五秒就好
Bathroom break? Just gimme 15 seconds.
抱歉  但是你还要赶飞机呢
Sorry, but you've got a flight to catch.
异常现象正在发生
噢  是吗  你也是
Oh, yeah? So do you!
见鬼  快回来
Hey! Dang it, get back here!
你们  抓住他
Men, get him!
不  你别想逃跑
No! You won't get away with this!
看我的  看我的
Gonna get ya! Gonna get ya!
-你知道神秘小屋在哪里吧  -知道
- You know where the Mystery Shack is? - Uh, yeah.
行  给你一百块
Okay, here's a hundred bucks.
开得离那里越远越好
Drive as far away from the Shack as possible,
就算警车追着你跑也别停下
and don't stop when the cops start chasing you!
他要逃走了
He's getting away!
很明显  快追那辆出租车
Obviously, follow that cab!
斯坦福逃脱了  正在逃亡中
Stanford escaped! He's at large!
我们要全镇大范围搜捕他  快点  动起来
We need to sweep the town! Move, move, move!
好的  苏斯  回想一下自己的计划
All right, Soos, remember the plan.
保护好机器  取得斯坦的信任
Protect the machine, earn Stan's trust,
被斯坦合法领养  然后改名为小斯坦
legally get adopted by Stan, change name to Stan Junior.
-苏斯  -孩子们  你们去哪儿啦
- Soos! - Oh, kids, where have you been?
你  你在这里干嘛呢
W-what are you doing here?
斯坦交给我一个任务  让我保护好这台售货机
Stan gave me a mission to protect this machine.
而且我也的确喜欢吃零食
Ha! And I thought I loved snacks!
苏斯  听着  这里要出大事了
Soos, listen. Something huge is going on here.
如果斯坦隐藏了什么危险的秘密
If Stan is hiding some dangerous secret,
我们必须查明真相
we need to find out what it is!
-希望你能让开  -对  让我们过去
- I need you to step aside. - Yeah, just let us through
然后我们就能证明这只是个误会了
so we can prove this is all just a big misunderstanding.
孩子们  我知道这很疯狂
Guys, I know this seems crazy,
但我答应过斯坦  要用自己的生命保护它
but I promised Stan I would guard this with my life.
抱歉  苏斯
I'm sorry, Soos.
荧光粉攻击  看着很美  伤得很痛
Attack glitter! It's pretty, but it hurts!
-求你了  苏斯  -拜托  苏斯
- Please, Soos! - C'mon, Soos!
别这样  我不想和你们打
Aw, c'mon, I don't wanna fight you guys!
这会让我比你们更受伤
This hurts me more than it hurts you!
说真的  我比你们痛得多
Seriously, it hurts me way more than it hurts you.
这是电子游戏里面才会发生的事吧
It's like something from a video game.
-或者梦里  -噩梦里
- Or a dream. - Or a nightmare.
我必须在一切发生之前及时赶到
I gotta be there when it happens!
我们是在做梦吗  来个人叫醒我吧
Guys, are we dreaming? Somebody wake me up.
这不可能吧
This... can't be real.
我不明白  为什么派恩斯先生会有这种东西
I don't understand. Why would Mr. Pines have all this?
这里和森林中的地下室好像
It's just like that bunker in the woods.
但是他在神秘小屋的地下干什么呢
But what is it doing underneath the Mystery Shack?
好吧  他拥有一个硕大无比的实验室
Okay, okay, so he's got a huge, gigantic lab.
也不是什么坏事啊
That doesn't mean anything bad.
每个人都有秘密
Everyone's got secrets!
他依旧是斯坦  爱我们的斯坦叔公
It's still Stan, and he loves us.
我们也爱他  不是吗
And we love him, right?
不可能  这不可能
Can't be... it's impossible.
另外两本日志
The other two journals?!
一直以来  一直以来都在斯坦手中
All this time, all this time, Stan had them?!
真是不敢相信  他对我们讲过真话吗
I can't believe it! Was anything he said to us real?!
-为什么他有这些日志  -或许他是作者
- Why would he have those journals?! - Maybe he's the author.
或许他是从作者那儿偷来的
Or maybe he stole them from the author!
也许他之所以有那么多假身份
Maybe the reason he has all of those fake IDs
是因为他是一个犯罪高手
is because he is a master criminal,
这个机器是他的终极计划
and this machine is his master plan!
这部机器本来应该创造知识
但它太强大了
这个设备
如果完全运转起来
可能撕裂我们的宇宙
我一直都弄错了
绝对不能落入坏人手中
时钟走到零的那一刻
天地万物将会毁灭
彻底的全球大毁灭！
“我一直都弄错了”
"I was wrong the whole time."
“这部机器本来应该创造知识”
"The machine was meant to create knowledge,"
“但它实在太强大”
"but it is too powerful!"
“我被骗了  现在已经太晚了”
"I was deceived, and now it is too late!"
“这个设备  如果完全运转起来”
"The device, if fully operational,"
“可能撕裂我们的宇宙”
"could tear our universe apart!"
“绝对不能落入坏人手中”
"It must not fall into the wrong hands."
“时钟走到零的那一刻  天地万物将会毁灭”
"If the clock ever reaches zero, our universe is doomed."
这是最终倒数计时  就像他们常唱的那首歌
It's the final countdown! Just like they always sung about!
警告！
极端用法  不推荐！
手动制动  故障保护
那些特工说得对  我们必须关掉它
The agents were right! We have to shut it down!
在那儿  快点
There! Quick!
拧钥匙  一起拧
Turn these! Together!
就是这个  停止开关
That's it! The shutdown switch!
一切都要结束了
This all stops now!
别碰那个按钮
Don't touch that button!
迪普  快走开
Dipper, just back away.
别按那个关闭按钮  你们必须相信我
Please don't press that shutdown button. You gotta trust me.
我为什么还要相信你
And I should trust you, why?
你偷了放射性废料
After you stole radioactive waste,
之前还骗了我们一整个夏天
after you lied to us all summer!
我都不清楚你是谁
I don't even know who you are!
听着  我知道这一切看上去很疯狂
Look, I know this all seems nuts,
但是那个机器不能关
but I need that machine to stay on.
如果你们能给我个机会解释
If you just let me explain...
不  找个东西抓住
Oh! Oh, no! Brace yourselves!
倒计时三十五秒
T-minus 35 seconds.
迪普
Dipper!
梅宝  快点  关了它
Mabel! Hurry! Shut it down!
不行
No!
梅宝  等等  梅宝
Mabel, Mabel, wait! Stop!
苏斯  你在干什么  我给你下了命令
Soos, what are you doing? I gave you an order!
对不起  派恩斯先生  如果这是你真名的话
Sorry, Mr. Pines, if that is your real name,
现在我有了一个新任务  保护孩子们
but I have a new mission now, protecting these kids!
苏斯  你这个傻瓜  放开我
Soos, you idiot, let me go!
-放开我  拜托  -梅宝  快按那个红按钮
- Let me go! C'mon! - Mabel, press the red button!
-关了它  -不  不行  你们得相信我
- Shut it down! - No, you can't! You gotta trust me!
斯坦叔公  我都不知道你是不是我的叔公
Grunkle Stan, I don't even know if you're my Grunkle!
我也想相信你  但是
I wanna believe you, but...
听我说  还记得今天早上
Then listen to me. Remember this morning,
我说我要告诉你们一件事
when I said I wanted to tell you guys something?
倒计时  二十秒
T-minus 20 seconds.
我想说  你们也许会听到关于我的坏消息
I wanted to say that you're gonna hear some bad things about me,
其中有一些是真的  但是相信我
and some of 'em are true, but trust me,
我所做的一切
everything I've worked for,
我所关心的一切  都是为了这个家
everything I care about, it's all for this family.
梅宝  他撒谎的话怎么办
Mabel, what if he's lying?
这个机器会毁了整个宇宙  你好好想想
This thing could destroy the universe! Listen to your head!
看着我的眼睛  梅宝
Look into my eyes, Mabel!
你真的觉得我是个坏人吗
You really think I'm a bad guy?
他在撒谎  快关了机器  快
He's lying! Shut it down, now!
-梅宝  求你了  -十  九
- Mabel, please! - Ten, nine...
斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan...
六  五
Six, five...
我相信你
I trust you.
梅宝  你疯了吗  我们都会
Mabel, are you crazy?! We're all gonna...
一
One.
不要啊
Nooo!
什么  他是谁
W-What? Who is that?
日志的作者
The author of the journals...
我兄弟
... my brother.
这种情节是不是我们之中一个人该晕倒了
Is this the part where one of us faints?
包在我身上
Oh, I am so on it, dude.